Sometimes the greatest journey is the distance between two people.
The Painted Veil is a romance, drama film directed by John Curran.
A British medical doctor fights a cholera outbreak in a small Chinese village, while
also being trapped at home in a loveless marriage to an unfaithful wife.
Dr. Walter Fane, played by Edward Norton.
Kitty Fane, played by Naomi Watts.
Charlie Townsend, played by Liev Schreiber.
Mr. Waddington, played by Toby Jones.
Mother Superior, played by Diana Rigg.
Colonel Yu, played by Anthony Wong Chau-Sang.
The Painted Veil is a 2006 drama film directed by John Curran.
The screenplay by Ron Nyswaner is based on the
1925 novel of the same title by W.
Somerset Maugham.
Edward Norton, Naomi Watts, Toby Jones, Anthony Wong Chau Sang
and Liev Schreiber appear in the leading roles.
This is the third film adaptation of the Maugham book, following a 1934 film starring Greta Garbo and Herbert Marshall and a 1957 version called The Seventh Sin with Bill Travers and Eleanor Parker, both of these
aforementioned are originally produced by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (since WB's sister company, Turner Entertainment currently owns the rights for the first 2 film adaptations, based on the original novel of the same name).
The film explores themes of infidelity, china, based on
novel or book, shanghai, china, nun.
The tone is emotional.